[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Why don't you like your picture?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "like", "your", "picture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Probably because I didn't like the way I looked.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "because", "I", "did", "n't", "like", "the", "way", "I", "looked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "What was it like for you last night when you went on there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "for", "you", "last", "night", "when", "you", "went", "on", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "You know I had -- I had a really good time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "had", "--", "I", "had", "a", "really", "good", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Did you feel awkward when that happens?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "awkward", "when", "that", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Do you think -- do you think he got it by the end?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "--", "do", "you", "think", "he", "got", "it", "by", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I think he was starting to get it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "was", "starting", "to", "get", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Do you think maybe a few more lessons?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "maybe", "a", "few", "more", "lessons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "I think he was starting -- yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "was", "starting", "--", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "What memories does it bring back to you if anything?", "question_tokens": ["What", "memories", "does", "it", "bring", "back", "to", "you", "if", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "You know most of the memories that I have of that time was backstage.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "most", "of", "the", "memories", "that", "I", "have", "of", "that", "time", "was", "backstage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "-- part of a famous family?", "question_tokens": ["--", "part", "of", "a", "famous", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "ONO: No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["ONO", ":", "No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "When you can start to remember, what kind of girl were you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "can", "start", "to", "remember", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "girl", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I was -- I mean I guess what you would call a classic tomboy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "mean", "I", "guess", "what", "you", "would", "call", "a", "classic", "tomboy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Or did you just feel odd?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "did", "you", "just", "feel", "odd", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I felt like it wasn't right for me, but at that point I mean, I didn't know -- I didn't know about, you know, being transgender.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "felt", "like", "it", "was", "n't", "right", "for", "me", ",", "but", "at", "that", "point", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "about", ",", "you", "know", ",", "being", "transgender", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Did that make it more difficult for you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "make", "it", "more", "difficult", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "No, I don't think it really made it -- I think that was kind of incidental.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "really", "made", "it", "--", "I", "think", "that", "was", "kind", "of", "incidental", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "And you weren't attracted to boys at all?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "were", "n't", "attracted", "to", "boys", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Never, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "What was the experience like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "experience", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Just kind of bland, really.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "kind", "of", "bland", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "To prove to yourself that you'd at least try it?", "question_tokens": ["To", "prove", "to", "yourself", "that", "you", "'d", "at", "least", "try", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "No, it wasn't -- no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "--", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Does that feel natural or normal to you at the time?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "feel", "natural", "or", "normal", "to", "you", "at", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "It does, but there's an expectation of the girls that I'm going out with, that I'm supposed to act like a girl, too.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", ",", "but", "there", "'s", "an", "expectation", "of", "the", "girls", "that", "I", "'m", "going", "out", "with", ",", "that", "I", "'m", "supposed", "to", "act", "like", "a", "girl", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "At what point does the confusion you have when you think you're a lesbian start to transform into there's something else here?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "does", "the", "confusion", "you", "have", "when", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "a", "lesbian", "start", "to", "transform", "into", "there", "'s", "something", "else", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "And at what point do you work out what that something else may be?", "question_tokens": ["And", "at", "what", "point", "do", "you", "work", "out", "what", "that", "something", "else", "may", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "WP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "For me it was a pretty long process, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "me", "it", "was", "a", "pretty", "long", "process", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Nice and flat, huh?", "question_tokens": ["Nice", "and", "flat", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "You know what?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "That's correct?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "That is correct, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "correct", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "How did she react?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "she", "react", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "And again, this was over -- we talked about it over time.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "again", ",", "this", "was", "over", "--", "we", "talked", "about", "it", "over", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "No, I think she -- I think when I was really young, she thought I was going to grow up and be gay.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "she", "--", "I", "think", "when", "I", "was", "really", "young", ",", "she", "thought", "I", "was", "going", "to", "grow", "up", "and", "be", "gay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "When you walk around, are people supportive to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "walk", "around", ",", "are", "people", "supportive", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "VBP", "NNS", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Very.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "I mean that's a remarkable sign of our times, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "that", "'s", "a", "remarkable", "sign", "of", "our", "times", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "It is really.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Does that make you feel good?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "It feels great, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "feels", "great", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "You didn't have a clue really, did you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "have", "a", "clue", "really", ",", "did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Well, early on in our relationship, he told me -- actually, I was told by a friend of his that he was indeed transgender.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "early", "on", "in", "our", "relationship", ",", "he", "told", "me", "--", "actually", ",", "I", "was", "told", "by", "a", "friend", "of", "his", "that", "he", "was", "indeed", "transgender", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "And what was your honest reaction when he said that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "your", "honest", "reaction", "when", "he", "said", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "I compartmentalized it and put it away.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "compartmentalized", "it", "and", "put", "it", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "I mean -- that's quite something, to compartmentalize it, is it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "--", "that", "'s", "quite", "something", ",", "to", "compartmentalize", "it", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "It's amazing when I can compartmentalize on that.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "amazing", "when", "I", "can", "compartmentalize", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "The great advantage of having you as his girlfriend is -- I think you're bisexual, right?", "question_tokens": ["The", "great", "advantage", "of", "having", "you", "as", "his", "girlfriend", "is", "--", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "bisexual", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Yes, that's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "-- right now is, do you?", "question_tokens": ["--", "right", "now", "is", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I find him more attractive as a man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "find", "him", "more", "attractive", "as", "a", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "As it was all unfurling, when it came out of its compartmentalization.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "it", "was", "all", "unfurling", ",", "when", "it", "came", "out", "of", "its", "compartmentalization", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Did you have arguments?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "arguments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "OK, well, there are two components.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", ",", "well", ",", "there", "are", "two", "components", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "What about psychologically?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "psychologically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Well, emotionally we went through a lot of work.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "emotionally", "we", "went", "through", "a", "lot", "of", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Well, without being too query here, but it's the kind of question I guess most viewers must be thinking, as your sex life been affected adversely or for the good by all this?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "without", "being", "too", "query", "here", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "the", "kind", "of", "question", "I", "guess", "most", "viewers", "must", "be", "thinking", ",", "as", "your", "sex", "life", "been", "affected", "adversely", "or", "for", "the", "good", "by", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "For the good.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "the", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "That's a remarkable thing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "remarkable", "thing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "It can't always be the case.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "ca", "n't", "always", "be", "the", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Is part of the reason that you feel able to deal with it, Jennifer, that he's happier?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "part", "of", "the", "reason", "that", "you", "feel", "able", "to", "deal", "with", "it", ",", "Jennifer", ",", "that", "he", "'s", "happier", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "You know what's going on?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Is that a patronizing thing to say?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "patronizing", "thing", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "That's a compliment.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "compliment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "No, I was always Chaz, with you.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "was", "always", "Chaz", ",", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Why was that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Well, I can't blame it solely on Chaz's transition.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "blame", "it", "solely", "on", "Chaz", "'s", "transition", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "For you, Chaz, when you saw Jennifer fall off the wagon, did it worry you that perhaps the stress of everything that you had put her through was now coming out in alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["For", "you", ",", "Chaz", ",", "when", "you", "saw", "Jennifer", "fall", "off", "the", "wagon", ",", "did", "it", "worry", "you", "that", "perhaps", "the", "stress", "of", "everything", "that", "you", "had", "put", "her", "through", "was", "now", "coming", "out", "in", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP$", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Actually, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chaz", "Jennifer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "And how are things right now?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "are", "things", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Really good.", "answer_tokens": ["Really", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Are you going to get married now?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "get", "married", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "goodness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Can we talk about children?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "talk", "about", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "People think I'm a -- idiot, you know?", "question_tokens": ["People", "think", "I", "'m", "a", "--", "idiot", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Sometimes, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Did it even hurt?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "even", "hurt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "No, it was good.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "was", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Greater love, there's no woman that can do that, right?", "question_tokens": ["Greater", "love", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "woman", "that", "can", "do", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Do you ever miss the female Chaz?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "miss", "the", "female", "Chaz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Not so much any more.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "so", "much", "any", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "From a technical point of view, are you now a straight guy?", "question_tokens": ["From", "a", "technical", "point", "of", "view", ",", "are", "you", "now", "a", "straight", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Sure, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "And you can't be a lesbian any more, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "ca", "n't", "be", "a", "lesbian", "any", "more", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "I'm a bisexual woman.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "bisexual", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Do you amuse yourselves when you explain all this to people who just sort of can't get it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "amuse", "yourselves", "when", "you", "explain", "all", "this", "to", "people", "who", "just", "sort", "of", "ca", "n't", "get", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "We amused Dave.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "amused", "Dave", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "What did you think watching that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "watching", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I thought it was great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "it", "was", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Have you talked about it?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "talked", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "I would like to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "like", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Are you legally now able to marry as a man and wife?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "legally", "now", "able", "to", "marry", "as", "a", "man", "and", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "We are, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "And would you choose to do that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "would", "you", "choose", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "I think that we probably will.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "probably", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Is there a window here that we're talking about?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "window", "here", "that", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "There's no ultimatum.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "ultimatum", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Within a year?", "question_tokens": ["Within", "a", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Yeah, it really has -- not to make excuses, but we went through a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "it", "really", "has", "--", "not", "to", "make", "excuses", ",", "but", "we", "went", "through", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "That will be some wedding, don't you think?", "question_tokens": ["That", "will", "be", "some", "wedding", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "I hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Have you ever always thought you may do that one day?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "always", "thought", "you", "may", "do", "that", "one", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "It's funny because we do differ on our -- how we would like to get married.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "funny", "because", "we", "do", "differ", "on", "our", "--", "how", "we", "would", "like", "to", "get", "married", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "So the obvious question is would you like to do that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "the", "obvious", "question", "is", "would", "you", "like", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Well, Piers, I mean, great timing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "great", "timing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "Should we get to a stage within the year-long window that Chaz has now said he will be held to, and we do get to that church and you are asked formally to be the officiator, would you do it?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "we", "get", "to", "a", "stage", "within", "the", "year-long", "window", "that", "Chaz", "has", "now", "said", "he", "will", "be", "held", "to", ",", "and", "we", "do", "get", "to", "that", "church", "and", "you", "are", "asked", "formally", "to", "be", "the", "officiator", ",", "would", "you", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Wow, you know, I honestly would be deeply honored to do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "honestly", "would", "be", "deeply", "honored", "to", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chaz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "Would it be right to assume that he would have been equally tolerant by this turn of events?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "be", "right", "to", "assume", "that", "he", "would", "have", "been", "equally", "tolerant", "by", "this", "turn", "of", "events", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "I -- it's so hard to guess how Sonny would have felt about this, you know, any more than anything else, after he's been gone for 13 years.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "it", "'s", "so", "hard", "to", "guess", "how", "Sonny", "would", "have", "felt", "about", "this", ",", "you", "know", ",", "any", "more", "than", "anything", "else", ",", "after", "he", "'s", "been", "gone", "for", "13", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Is that an unfair thing of me to observe?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "an", "unfair", "thing", "of", "me", "to", "observe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "I -- You know, this is family.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "You", "know", ",", "this", "is", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Do you hope that the publicity surrounding Chaz's story may lead to a more tolerant, dare I say, liberal attitude towards this kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "hope", "that", "the", "publicity", "surrounding", "Chaz", "'s", "story", "may", "lead", "to", "a", "more", "tolerant", ",", "dare", "I", "say", ",", "liberal", "attitude", "towards", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "I don't want to throw out any political terms and label anybody anything here.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "throw", "out", "any", "political", "terms", "and", "label", "anybody", "anything", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chaz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "To sum up, love conquers all, right, Chaz?", "question_tokens": ["To", "sum", "up", ",", "love", "conquers", "all", ",", "right", ",", "Chaz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "Absolutely, it does.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "it", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chaz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "We got a deal?", "question_tokens": ["We", "got", "a", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "We've got a deal, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "got", "a", "deal", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "What was going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Man, it's more than one incident actually.", "answer_tokens": ["Man", ",", "it", "'s", "more", "than", "one", "incident", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 812, "question": "Is it one of the downsides of fame, that you were talking about?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "one", "of", "the", "downsides", "of", "fame", ",", "that", "you", "were", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 813, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "What's your point?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 841, "question": "You don't think she meant it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "think", "she", "meant", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 842, "answer": "I think she meant it to a certain extent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "meant", "it", "to", "a", "certain", "extent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 843, "question": "What does she do for a living?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "she", "do", "for", "a", "living", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 844, "answer": "Movie star, actor.", "answer_tokens": ["Movie", "star", ",", "actor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 845, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "An actor.", "answer_tokens": ["An", "actor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 848, "question": "You think it was an act?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "it", "was", "an", "act", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 849, "answer": "I think, you know, that whole -- people have to live in that world and --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "whole", "--", "people", "have", "to", "live", "in", "that", "world", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 850, "question": "Are you glad to be out of it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "glad", "to", "be", "out", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 851, "answer": "Oh, man, 100 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "man", ",", "100", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110512pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "They are all pretty fake, is that what you're saying?", "question_tokens": ["They", "are", "all", "pretty", "fake", ",", "is", "that", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "It's just pretend.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "pretend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]